♪ It seems today that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in
movies and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those good
old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a... Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
Hi there. It's me, Peter.
You know, when it comes to
making dreams come alive,
there used to be nothing
like the movies.
So we thought it would be fun to ask
a few visionary Hollywood
directors to create his...
Let's be honest, his...
Own unique version of the
same Family Guy story,
"Peter Gets Fired."
Of the countless
directors we contacted,
three did not say no immediately,
and I got a weird message
from Paul Verhoeven
that I could not understand.
Ah, Pieoter, habinsky Vermhoeven.
Kibbensme comfurdle. Stupf.
I've listened to that
over a hundred times now.
I-I got nothin'.
Anyway, here's our first director,
Quentin Tarantino.
♪ Hey, well, I'm the
friendly stranger ♪
♪ In the black sedan, won't
you hop inside my car? ♪
♪ I got pictures, got
candy, I'm a lovable man ♪
♪ And I can take you
to the nearest star ♪
♪ I'm your vehicle, baby ♪
♪ I'll take you
anywhere you wanna go ♪
♪ I'm your vehicle, woman ♪
♪ By now I'm sure you know ♪
- ♪ That I love ya ♪
- ♪ Love ya ♪
- ♪ I need ya ♪
- ♪ Need ya ♪
♪ I want you, got to have you, child ♪
♪ Great God in heaven,
you know I love you... ♪
- What's in your lunch?
- Pizza.
From home or from a place?
A place.
♪ Well, if you wants
to be a movie star ♪
♪ I'll get a ticket to Hollywood. ♪
Griffin, you're three hours late.
Stop trying to be a clock, you
ain't got the face for it.
I've had enough of your nonsense.
Here's Christoph Waltz to
fire you in a weird accent.
Yer fi-yerd!
It's a clich├й.
You think you can fire me?
I'm taking this keg as payback.
Cinema is an event.
- Where's my family?
- Dead. All of them.
Oh, my God, where am I?
- What happened?
- Ugh! Coma breath.
Coma?! How long was I out?
- What year is this?
- It's whatever year
Quentin Tarantino used
to watch television.
Well, can I go home?
Well, you're not really ready,
but if it's for revenge,
you can stab me with this scalpel
- and then run out.
- Thanks.
Oh, that was unnecessary but cool.
So awesome!
Ah, so close.
No, this is better.
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah. ♪
Somebody order a wet-haired black guy
to help with your
revenge and sometimes
Speak louder than necessary?
♪ ♪
Angela?
We got business.
Sorry, that's my car alarm.
Cleveland, turn that off!
I'm pressing the button.
Y-You got to put the
keys in the ignition.
I've been doing that, but...
Oh, there we go.
Tricia Takanawa 88s!
♪ ♪
Peter, I'm standing here because I am
the only Asian recurring
character on the series.
- ♪ Get on up ♪
- ♪ Get up ♪
- ♪ Stay on the scene ♪
- ♪ Get on up ♪
♪ Like a lovin' machine ♪
♪ Get on up ♪
- ♪ Get up ♪
- ♪ Get on up ♪
- ♪ Taste ♪
- ♪ Of piano ♪
- ♪ Get on up. ♪
Peter, you can tell I'm different
because my weapon is different.
Oh, well, then, maybe I won't be able
to chop your head off.
Oh, yep.
♪ ♪
Opera music makes violence classy.
Of course.
That!
♪ What's new, pussycat? ♪
♪ Whoa, whoa, whoa ♪
♪ What's new, pussycat? Whoa. ♪
Welcome back to our special episode,
featuring famous directors' versions
of the same Family Guy
story, "Peter Gets Fired."
I'm still here in front
of the Hollywood Sign,
but I've asked the cameraman
to adjust the shot
so that you can only see "wood."
I thought that would be hilarious.
You know why? 'Cause of boners.
Anyway, our next director
is Wes Anderson,
a guy who makes you feel
like you ate a pot brownie
and woke up in a greeting card.
Mmm.
Yum-yum-yum-yum-yum-yum-yum.
On a March day, with a
temperature of 64 degrees,
my father lost his position
with the Pawtucket
Brothers Brewery Company,
near our village in central Quahogia.
Needless to say, it would
change our lives forever.
What does it say? I
can't read spaghetti.
You're relieved of your position.
I see. And what's to
happen to my play?
The opening is only days away.
The play's off.
With no discernible reaction,
my father made his way home to
deliver the news to my mother.
Let me tell you about my house.
We lived in a New England cottage
that was inside a vintage Army tent,
that was inside a
decommissioned submarine,
that was all inside an
old airplane hangar.
I've lost my position
with the Pawtucket
Brothers Brewery Company.
And the play is off.
We have to inform the children.
My brother Chris had spent his life
conjoining his twin loves,
medicine and escape artistry.
Eureka.
A possible cure.
Do you want to do a Spider-Man kiss?
Our dog Brian had been
making a name for himself
on the pickleball court.
And that's match for Gene Porterfield.
Are those marking sole shoes?
I'd like to officially
file a grievance.
Brian had quietly become
the most successful
grievance filer in league history.
I'll be there right away.
The exterior of our house
is a lighthouse now.
Inside's the same.
Okay, back to the story.
I've summoned you all and arranged you
in a perfectly symmetrical
form in front of me
to tell you some important news.
I've been relieved of my
position at the brewery.
What of the play?
The play is postponed, indefinitely.
No, Mr. Griffin.
You need to do this play.
We'll help you.
But I've lost access to the brewery.
That's where the whole piece is set.
Maybe it doesn't have to be.
But that's where the
free tape and paper is.
I'll buy you new tape and paper.
The play is back on.
On an overcast Thursday afternoon,
my father presented his play,
one of the most compelling
stories of the 1980s,
Max Dugan Returns.
Max, you've returned!
I have.
This took a lot of work.
My father passed away in the
spring of his 43rd year,
and was put to rest in
the family graveyard.
He died chasing a Pok├йmon
across a busy street.
♪ ♪
Hey there. It's me again.
Wouldn't it be great if
Wes Anderson's movies
were actually that short?
Anyway, the Hollywood Sign is
more historic than you think.
On this very spot, 52 years ago,
a piece of beef jerky was
planted in the ground
and watered with Red Bull.
A speedboat erupted from the soil,
and in that speedboat...
was Michael Bay.
♪ ♪
This already doesn't make sense.
You're fired, Griffin,
for destroying company property.
Tell it to my tongue.
Mr. President, we have a situation.
The Decepticons plan to destroy
the Seven Wonders of the World,
starting with the Hagia Sophia.
The what? Is that even one
of the Seven Wonders?
The Decepticons have
only one weakness.
They're allergic to beer.
I don't like the taste either so much.
That chest plate is where
they're most vulnerable.
If we could find someone
strong enough to throw a keg
with enough force, we
might have a shot.
The only problem is,
there's not a man alive
who can throw a keg with
that kind of force.
There may be one.
I wonder who it is.
♪ ♪
Our top story, stopping the
Decepticons with beer?
According to our sources,
the search is underway
for a man strong enough
to throw a keg with enough force
to save the Seven
Wonders of the World.
What took you so long?
There was a train and I
like to count the cars.
It was a big one.
Me, too. That is fun.
But you're wasting
your time coming here.
I don't throw kegs anymore.
Who's this?
What are you wearing?
That's my funeral shirt.
Look, Peter, I didn't want
to ask you to do this
because of that maverick
but awesome thing you did
in the battle war of the past.
Is this the stuff you didn't
want me to ask you about?
I told you not to ask me about that.
He went rogue and saved
everyone's lives,
but he didn't do it by the book.
Is that why he can't get an erection?
Everyone stop talking about me!
Listen, it's not me that's asking,
it's America.
Tell America my answer is "no."
Now, if you'll excuse me, I
have to go change my mind
in the shower.
♪ Peter's country needs him ♪
♪ But he just doesn't know ♪
♪ He's scared he'll miss his shows ♪
♪ And he's expecting a UPS package ♪
♪ Who's gonna water his plants? ♪
♪ He's got a lot of balls in the air ♪
♪ That's for sure. ♪
Hold on!
Damn it, I'm in.
But I do things my way,
and I pick my crew.
Deal. Now let me sit
sideways on your motorcycle
like a Vietnamese woman,
and let's get out of here.
Still trying to put the
world back together, I see.
Hello, Peter.
We're not joining your team.
I'm putting together a team.
- We're in.
- Good.
Let's shake hands like tough guys.
Some of your sweat went in my mouth.
Oh, hello, Peter.
I was just out back
working in the garden.
Oh, yeah?
Trying to grow some balls?
Okay, okay.
Play nice, boys.
Love the cookie-cutter house
you and Poindexter got here.
Never pegged you for a burbs dweller.
Peter, you used to live here.
That was a long time ago.
It was two months ago.
Two months is a long time
when you don't sleep and
only eat ground beef.
Did you tell Chris about my mission?
I thought you should.
This is my favorite
out of all the Seven
Wonders of the World.
The Hagia Sophia.
It's like God made a
basilica for himself.
Dad, nothing bad will ever happen
to the Hagia Sophia, right?
Not on my watch.
The Decepticons' second target
has been announced.
It's Machu Picchu.
City in the clouds.
Inca Empire.
When did our kids get so
obsessed with the Seven Wonders?
They learned it from you.
Got to go, babe.
Pete.
Save that basilica.
According to the calculations
on my Microsoft Surface,
they have advanced
cloaking technology.
The Microsoft Surface confirms it.
Microsoft Surface.
My Samsung Gear S2 watch
says the same thing.
We came from outer space
to step on church stuff.
That does it.
Let's have a fight with so many
quick shots and close-ups,
you can't tell what's going on.
♪ Up ♪
♪ To break it back down ♪
♪ We're building it up ♪
♪ To burn it down ♪
♪ We can't wait ♪
♪ To burn it to the ground ♪
♪ The colors conflict. ♪
Peter, don't.
It's suicide.
Take care of my kids' bikes.
They're expensive.
♪ ♪
Oh, my God!
I can't believe Peter's gone.
I never got to repeat to
him the line he said to me
earlier in the film that
has taken on new meaning
in the context of all
that has happened.
Today is the day we honor
the late Peter Griffin,
the hero who saved the Seven
Wonders of the World.
Who's that ugly son of a bitch?
Peter, you're alive.
But-but how?
You were blown into a million pieces.
Luckily, I know a couple
of pretty good welders.
Wait, they-they welded
you back together?
A-And they knew you were
alive the whole time?
You want to ask questions or you
want to do it in a cemetery?
Is... is everything all right?
Yeah, no, I-I think I'm just tired
from all the flying back and forth.
Maybe we just talk
here for a little bit,
and then you can tell everyone
that I functioned as I should.
Yeah, uh, okay.
So, which director thing
was your favorite?
Mine was this one.
Oh, honestly, I-I didn't
care for the episode.
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru